Coming.
آت.
That wasn't the first time
لم تكن هذه هي المرة الأولى
that my life was turned upside down.
أن حياتي انقلبت رأسًا على عقب.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
I learned that
تعلمت أن
one day is all it takes
يوم واحد هو كل ما يتطلبه الأمر
for my entire life
طوال حياتي
to be turned upside down.
أن تنقلب رأسًا على عقب.
I learned that…
تعلمت أن…
Hi.
أهلاً.
Long time no see.
وقت طويل لا رؤية.
…for the first time 20 years ago.
... لأول مرة منذ 20 عامًا.
ON DUTY FOR YOUR SAFETY AND HAPPINESS YOUNGSAN POLICE STATION
واجب من أجل سلامتك وسعادتك في مركز شرطة يونغ سان
Hey, kid.
يا طفل.
Is something wrong?
هل هناك خطأ؟
Do you need help?
هل تحتاج مساعدة؟
Wait, is that…
انتظر ، هل هذا ...
blood on your clothes?
الدم على ملابسك؟
Hey!
يا!
YOUNGSAN EXPRESS BUS TERMINAL
محطة الحافلات YOUNGSAN EXPRESS
LEGAL NAME CHANGE FORM
استمارة تغيير الاسم القانوني
And
و
I heard…
سمعت…
NEW NAME KIM HYE-JOO
الاسم الجديد كيم هاي جو
…that name again…
... هذا الاسم مرة أخرى ...
Kim Jae-eun.
كيم جاي يون.
…for the first time in 20 years.
... لأول مرة منذ 20 عامًا.
Or should I say…
أو ينبغي أن أقول…
Kim Hye-joo?
كيم هي-جو؟
You murderer.
أنت قاتل.
CONFRONTATION
مواجهة
How have you been?
كيف كان حالك؟
Right.
الصحيح.
I know it's late, but congratulations on your marriage.
أعلم أن الوقت متأخر ، لكن مبروك على زواجك.
The wife of an assemblyman?
زوجة عضو مجلس النواب؟
That's amazing.
هذا مذهل.
You had reached out to my chief advisor
لقد تواصلت مع كبير مستشاري
but I wanted to meet you personally.
لكنني أردت مقابلتك شخصيًا.
Look…
ينظر…
Is that your daughter?
هل تلك ابنتك؟
No.
لا.
Then who is she?
ثم من هي؟
She's a kid I know.
إنها طفلة أعرفها.
Yes, she's just a kid I know.
نعم ، إنها مجرد طفلة أعرفها.
Look, Seung-hee.
انظر ، سونغ هي.
I'm a bit busy today,
أنا مشغول قليلاً اليوم ،
so let's talk…
اذن هيا نتحدث…
Let's talk another time, okay?
لنتحدث مرة أخرى ، حسنًا؟
All right.
حسنا.
Let me get your number then.
دعني أحصل على رقمك بعد ذلك.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Save my number.
حفظ رقم هاتفي.
I'll call you.
سوف اتصل بك.
Okay.
تمام.
It's so nice to see you.
من اللطيف رؤيتك.
I missed you,
أفتقدك،
my friend.
صديقي.
See you later.
أراك لاحقًا.
Ms. Kim.
السيدة كيم.
Let's visit Ji-hoon some other time.
دعنا نزور Ji-hoon في وقت آخر.
I'm feeling unwell. I need to get some rest.
أشعر بتوعك.  أنا بحاجة للحصول على قسط من الراحة.
What?
لما؟
My name?
اسمي؟
Yes.
نعم.
I'm taking out a mortgage to fund the election campaign.
أنا آخذ رهنًا عقاريًا لتمويل الحملة الانتخابية.
I needed our resident registration forms
كنت بحاجة إلى استمارات تسجيل المقيمين لدينا
since the house is under both of our names,
بما أن المنزل تحت اسمينا ،
and yours said you had changed your name.
وقال لك أنك غيرت اسمك.
Kim Jae-eun?
كيم جاي يون؟
It's a pretty name. Why did you change it?
إنه اسم جميل.  لماذا قمت بتغييره؟
No reason.
بدون سبب.
"Kim Jae-eun."
"كيم جاي يون".
That's new.
ذلك جديد.
Go to bed first.
اذهب إلى الفراش أولاً.
I'll be in the study.
سأكون في الدراسة.
Thank you for reaching out to us.
شكر لتواصلك معنا.
I came here to tell you to stop what you're doing.
جئت إلى هنا لأخبرك أن توقف ما تفعله.
My mother-in-law has done nothing wrong.
حماتي لم ترتكب أي خطأ.
We can get into that later.
يمكننا الدخول في ذلك لاحقًا.
Are you originally from Youngsan?
هل انت اصلا من يونغسان؟
It's also my wife's hometown.
إنها أيضًا مسقط رأس زوجتي.
I see.
أرى.
She often talks about fond memories of Youngsan,
غالبًا ما تتحدث عن ذكريات جميلة ليونغسان ،
so whenever I meet people from there, I feel at home as well.
لذلك كلما قابلت أشخاصًا من هناك ، أشعر أنني في المنزل أيضًا.
But I try to stay professional
لكني أحاول أن أبقى محترفًا
and distinguish
وتميز
right from wrong.
بين الصواب والخطأ.
Now that we're acquainted, try to arrange a meal with him.
الآن بعد أن تعرفنا ، حاول ترتيب وجبة معه.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Sir, it's about Ji Seung-kyu's family.
سيدي ، الأمر يتعلق بعائلة جي سونغ كيو.
Ji Seung…
جي سونغ ...
Right, the medical student? What is it?
صحيح ، طالب الطب؟  ما هذا؟
His mother swallowed some pills.
ابتلعت والدته بعض الحبوب.
Do you think Mr. Nam's meeting with Mr. Choi didn't go very well?
هل تعتقد أن لقاء السيد نام بالسيد تشوي لم يسير على ما يرام؟
He's been looking kind of uneasy.
لقد كان يبدو مضطربًا نوعًا ما.
Right?
حق؟
What could it be?
ماذا يمكن أن يكون؟
ASSEMBLYMAN'S OFFICE
مكتب ASSEMBLYMAN
Thanks. Bye.
شكرًا.  الوداع.
They pumped her stomach, so her life is not in danger.
ضخوا بطنها حتى لا تكون حياتها في خطر.
Why did she do it?
لماذا هي فعلت هذا؟
I'm not sure.
لست واثق.
Well…
نحن سوف…
She must be either heartbroken over the loss of her son
يجب أن تكون إما حزينة بسبب فقدان ابنها
or shocked by the hateful comments.
أو صدمت من التعليقات البغيضة.
Every article about him had quite a few comments saying that he deserved to die.
كان لكل مقال عنه بعض التعليقات التي تقول إنه يستحق الموت.
I called them "hateful comments",
أسميتها "تعليقات الكراهية" ،
but that's the public sentiment.
لكن هذا هو الشعور العام.
So please don't blame yourself
لذا من فضلك لا تلوم نفسك
for what happened to him or his mother.
لما حدث له أو لأمه.
Are you thinking about Ji-hoon?
هل تفكر في جي-هون؟
How could I not?
كيف لا أستطيع؟
He must have received tens of thousands of hate comments.
لابد أنه تلقى عشرات الآلاف من التعليقات الكارهة.
Every time he did something wrong
في كل مرة فعل شيئًا خاطئًا
and even after his death.
وحتى بعد وفاته.
It's true that what he did was wrong,
صحيح أن ما فعله كان خطأ ،
and he should be scolded and punished for it.
وينبغي توبيخه ومعاقبته على ذلك.
But…
لكن…
NAM JOONG-DO MUST TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR HIS SON'S MISDEEDS AND STEP DOWN
يجب أن يتحمل نام جونغ-دو المسؤولية عن سوء معاملة ابنه وأن يتراجع
Most parents beg for mercy
يتوسل معظم الآباء من أجل الرحمة
when their children do something wrong…
عندما يرتكب أطفالهم شيئًا خاطئًا ...
I ask for him to be punished strictly by the law,
أطلب أن يعاقب القانون بصرامة ،
and I sincerely apologize as his father
وأنا أعتذر بصدق بصفتي والده
for failing to discipline him properly.
لفشله في تأديبه بشكل صحيح.
THE NATIONAL ASSEMBLY OF THE REPUBLIC OF KOREA
الجمعية الوطنية لجمهورية كوريا
…but I did the opposite.
... لكنني فعلت العكس.
Hi, honey.
هلا حبيبتي.
NAM APOLOGIZES FOR SON'S ASSAULT CASE AT PRESS CONFERENCE
حركة عدم الانحياز تعتذر عن جريمة الاعتداء التي تعرض لها ابنه في مؤتمر صحفي
And it hurt my wife greatly.
وقد آلم زوجتي كثيرا.
Don't give a criminal a narrative.
لا تعطي قصة لمجرم.
What?
لما؟
"Don't give a criminal a narrative."
"لا تعطِ مجرما رواية."
That's what the audience says these days
هذا ما يقوله الجمهور هذه الأيام
when characters in movies or dramas say something like that.
عندما تقول الشخصيات في الأفلام أو الدراما شيئًا من هذا القبيل.
They refuse to give criminals any room for pity
إنهم يرفضون إعطاء المجرمين أي مجال للشفقة
or being understood.
أو يجري فهمها.
That's the public sentiment.
هذا هو الشعور العام.
I have a heavy heart whenever I think of Ji-hoon,
لدي قلب حزين عندما أفكر في جي-هون ،
but that's the reality.
لكن هذا هو الواقع.
What I mean by that is,
ما أعنيه بذلك هو ،
you have to keep your pity, or any form of personal sentiments
عليك أن تحافظ على شفقتك ، أو أي شكل من أشكال المشاعر الشخصية
toward Ji-hoon or Ji Seung-kyu's mother, at home.
تجاه والدة Ji-hoon أو Ji Seung-kyu في المنزل.
You should only express it to your wife.
يجب عليك فقط التعبير عن ذلك لزوجتك.
You're not Ji-hoon's father right now.
أنت لست والد جي هون الآن.
You're an assemblyman with an election coming up.
أنت عضو في الجمعية مع انتخابات قادمة.
Just like you said, you have to stay professional.
كما قلت ، عليك أن تظل محترفًا.
If you were to lose your child,
إذا كنت ستفقد طفلك ،
what would you rather have the cause of death be?
ماذا تفضل أن يكون سبب الوفاة؟
Suicide, murder…
انتحار ، قتل ...
or an accident?
أو حادث؟
The last one would be the least painful.
سيكون الأخير هو الأقل إيلامًا.
It would be, wouldn't it?
سيكون ، أليس كذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
At least as a parent.
على الأقل كوالد.
She often talks about fond memories of Youngsan,
غالبًا ما تتحدث عن ذكريات جميلة ليونغسان ،
so whenever I meet people from there, I feel at home as well.
لذلك كلما قابلت أشخاصًا من هناك ، أشعر أنني في المنزل أيضًا.
-She ran away? -Yes.
-ركضت بعيدا؟  -نعم.
She left town as soon as she graduated.
غادرت المدينة بمجرد تخرجها.
She ran away from her crimes.
هربت من جرائمها.
SEOUL TO YOUNGSAN
سيول ليونغ سان
KIM JAE-EUN
كيم جاي-أون
You've been living a happy life, haven't you?
كنت تعيش حياة سعيدة ، أليس كذلك؟
NEW MESSAGE FROM SEUNG-HEE
رسالة جديدة من SEUNG-HEE
MEDICAL STUDENT COMMITS SUICIDE AFTER BEING EXPOSED BY NAM
انتحار الطلاب الطبيين بعد تعرضهم من قبل NAM
Your husband killed someone as well.
زوجك قتل شخصًا أيضًا.
By the way,
على فكرة،
does he know about your past?
هل يعرف عن ماضيك؟
INCOMING CALL
مكالمة واردة
-Hey, Seung-hee. -I saw the news.
مرحبًا سيونغ هي.  -شاهدت الخبر.
Hey.
يا.
Look, Seung-hee…
انظر ، سونغ هي ...
Did you think fleeing to Seoul and changing your name
هل فكرت في الهروب إلى سيول وتغيير اسمك
would cover up the murder you committed?
سوف تستر على جريمة القتل التي ارتكبتها؟
If that's what you wanted, you should have kept a low profile.
إذا كان هذا هو ما تريده ، كان يجب أن تظل بعيدًا عن الأنظار.
Did you think no one would recognize you
هل تعتقد أن لا أحد سيتعرف عليك
when you're the wife of an assemblyman?
عندما تكونين زوجة عضو مجلس النواب؟
Come to Youngsan.
تعال إلى يونغسان.
We should…
ينبغي لنا…
continue our little chat.
أكمل محادثتنا الصغيرة.
Come here tomorrow.
تعال هنا غدا.
And don't even think about running away.
ولا تفكر حتى في الهروب.
Seung-hee--
سيونغ هي -
YOUR HUSBAND KILLED SOMEONE AS WELL. DOES HE KNOW ABOUT YOUR PAST?
قتل زوجك شخصًا أيضًا.  هل يعرف عن ماضيك؟
Mom.
أم.
Hey, I'm home.
مرحبًا ، أنا في المنزل.
Where have you been all day?
أين كنت طوال اليوم؟
Sorry.
آسف.
I had to take care of something.
كان علي الاهتمام بشيء ما.
Mom.
أم.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Well…
نحن سوف…
I know we're supposed to go shopping for land tomorrow,
أعلم أنه من المفترض أن نذهب للتسوق لشراء الأرض غدًا ،
but can you go without me?
لكن هل يمكنك الذهاب بدوني؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Something's come up.
حدث شيء ما.
You're meeting your friends in the evening anyway.
أنت تقابل أصدقاءك في المساء على أي حال.
I'll go with you next time, okay?
سأذهب معك في المرة القادمة ، حسنًا؟
Just for tomorrow.
فقط للغد.
I wouldn't be of much help anyway.
لن أكون عونا كبيرا على أي حال.
Hey, is Ki-young home yet?
مرحبًا ، هل Ki-young منزل حتى الآن؟
"Ki-young"?
"كي يونغ"؟
You come home after spending the entire day out,
تعود إلى المنزل بعد قضاء اليوم بأكمله في الخارج ،
and the first person you ask about is your husband?
وأول شخص تسأل عنه هو زوجك؟
Are you not worried about me who's been at home all alone?
ألا تقلق علي من كنت في المنزل بمفردك؟
You two should have just gone to live in Australia without me.
كان من المفترض أن تذهبا للتو للعيش في أستراليا بدوني.
Mom.
أم.
Could you please stop saying that?
هل يمكنك التوقف عن قول ذلك من فضلك؟
I'm really sorry for saying I wanted to move to Australia.
أنا آسف حقًا لقولي إنني أردت الانتقال إلى أستراليا.
But I didn't go. So please--
لكنني لم أذهب.  إذن من فضلك--
I don't want to hear it.
لا اريد ان اسمعها.
You're the only child I have left after Seung-ho passed away,
أنت الطفل الوحيد الذي تركته بعد وفاة سونغ هو ،
but I don't want to talk to a heartless person like you anymore.
لكني لا أريد أن أتحدث إلى شخص بلا قلب مثلك بعد الآن.
I'll go by myself tomorrow.
سأذهب بنفسي غدا.
And I'll drop dead right there
وسوف أسقط ميتا هناك
-and go meet Seung-ho. -Mom.
- واذهب لمقابلة "سيونغ هو".  -أم.
Fine.
بخير.
I'll come with you, okay?
سوف آتي معك ، حسنًا؟
I'm sorry about everything and I'll come with you.
أنا آسف على كل شيء وسآتي معك.
So please just stop it, will you?
لذا من فضلك توقف فقط ، أليس كذلك؟
COME TO THIS ADDRESS
تعال إلى هذا العنوان
Come to this address at 7 p.m. tomorrow.
تعال إلى هذا العنوان في الساعة 7 مساءً غدًا.
You murderer.
أنت قاتل.
DELETE
حذف
YOU MURDERER
أنت قاتلة
DELETE FROM THIS DEVICE
احذف من هذا الجهاز
I'll revise the parts you mentioned today
سأقوم بمراجعة الأجزاء التي ذكرتها اليوم
and report back to you.
وإبلاغك بالرد.
Yes, that would be great.
نعم هذا سيكون أمرا رائعا.
But if I'm being honest,
لكن إذا كنت صادقًا ،
It seems a bit premature to discuss the next term's agenda
يبدو أنه من السابق لأوانه مناقشة أجندة الفصل المقبل
as we prepare for the upcoming election.
ونحن نستعد للانتخابات القادمة.
Not at all, sir.
لا إطلاقا يا سيدي.
You should definitely look far ahead.
يجب عليك بالتأكيد أن تنظر إلى الأمام بعيدًا.
I decided to work with you this term
قررت العمل معك في هذا المصطلح
because I saw you advocating for the underprivileged
لأنني رأيتك تدافع عن المحرومين
during your previous term.
خلال فترتك السابقة.
I didn't join to be here for just a single term.
لم أنضم لأكون هنا لفترة واحدة فقط.
You need to stay in politics
أنت بحاجة إلى البقاء في السياسة
and improve our country.
وتحسين بلادنا.
Absolutely.
على الاطلاق.
And don't worry about the election.
ولا تقلق بشأن الانتخابات.
We'll do all the legwork.
سنفعل كل الأعمال.
I've been jogging 30 minutes a day.
أمارس رياضة الجري لمدة 30 دقيقة في اليوم.
Take it easy.
خذها ببساطة.
Thank you for your encouragement.
شكرا لكم على تشجيعكم.
I'll do my best.
سافعل ما بوسعي.
-You got this, sir! -You got this.
-لديك هذا يا سيدي!  -لقد حصلت على هذا.
Why are you out here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
Ki-young.
كي يونغ.
Were you waiting for me?
هل كنت تنتظرني؟
You weren't coming home, so I thought you left me.
لم تكن عائدًا إلى المنزل ، لذلك اعتقدت أنك تركتني.
Do you want to go out for dinner tonight?
هل تريد الخروج لتناول العشاء الليلة؟
It's been a while.
لقد مر وقت طويل.
Maybe another time.
ربما في وقت أخر.
My mom is home alone.
أمي في المنزل وحدها.
Ki-young.
كي يونغ.
Things will…
الأشياء سوف ...
get better soon.
عجل بالشفاء.
Hey, come and eat.
مهلا ، تعال وكل.
Hye-joo isn't eating. She has a headache.
هاي جو لا تأكل.  لديها صداع.
Maybe she has a cold.
ربما كانت مصابة بنزلة برد.
Are you feeling better?
هل تشعر بتحسن؟
-Yes. -Go ahead and eat.
-نعم.  - امض قدما وتناول الطعام.
I'll eat after bringing her some porridge.
سوف آكل بعد أن أحضر لها بعض العصيدة.
I'll bring it to her.
سأحضرها لها.
What are you…
ما أنت…
Give me that. Why are you touching my phone?
أعطني هذا.  لماذا تلمس هاتفي؟
MISSED CALL FROM HUSBAND
مكالمة فائتة من الزوج
Don't come into my room or touch my stuff without my permission. Understand?
لا تدخل غرفتي أو تلمس أشيائي بدون إذني.  تفهم؟
Okay.
تمام.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Hi, honey.
هلا حبيبتي.
I missed your call.
فاتني إتصالك.
Sorry. What's up?
آسف.  ما أخبارك؟
What?
لما؟
My voice?
صوتي؟
No, I'm not sick.
لا ، أنا لست مريضا.
I think it's just a cold.
أعتقد أنه مجرد نزلة برد.
Were you just calling to check in?
هل كنت تتصل فقط لتسجيل الوصول؟
Okay.
تمام.
All right. See you later.
حسنا.  أراك لاحقًا.
Bye.
الوداع.
So please don't think about visiting Ji Seung-kyu's mother at the hospital.
لذا من فضلك لا تفكر في زيارة والدة جي سونغ كيو في المستشفى.
You'll only receive public backlash.
لن تتلقى سوى رد فعل عام عنيف.
-Mom. -Hey, Yoon-seo.
-أم.  مرحبا يون سيو.
Are you sick?
هل انت مريض؟
Did you catch a cold? Or is it something else?
هل أنت مصاب بالبرد؟  أو انه شيء اخر؟
No, I'm fine.
لا أنا بخير.
Did you eat?
هل أكلت؟
Yes. Are you hungry?
نعم.  هل انت جوعان؟
I already ate.
انا اكلت مسبقا.
Should I get you some medicine?
هل يجب أن أحضر لك بعض الأدوية؟
That's okay.
حسنا.
-Mom, don't be sick. -Yes?
- أمي ، لا تمرض.  -نعم؟
-Okay? -I'm not sick. I'm totally fine.
-تمام؟  -انا لست مريض.  أنا بخير تماما.
Are you sure?
هل أنت متأكد؟
How dare you?
كيف تجرؤ؟
How dare you come here?
كيف تجرؤ على المجيء إلى هنا؟
You killed my son!
لقد قتلت ابني!
Are you here to see if his mother died as well?
هل أنت هنا لترى ما إذا كانت والدته ماتت أيضًا؟
You have no right to come here, you murderer!
ليس لك الحق في المجيء إلى هنا ، أيها القاتل!
Say something, damn it.
قل شيئا ، تبا.
Why did you do that to Seung-kyu?
لماذا فعلت هذا لـ Seung-kyu؟
Being an assemblyman doesn't give you that right!
كونك عضو تجميع لا يمنحك هذا الحق!
Where's that badge of yours?
أين شارة لك؟
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Are you going to resign for what you've done?
هل ستستقيل بسبب ما قمت به؟
Are you?
أنت؟
I also
أنا أيضاً
lost my son recently.
لقد فقدت ابني مؤخرًا.
I'm not here today
لست هنا اليوم
as an assemblyman.
كعضو تجميع.
I'm here…
أنا هنا…
as a father…
كأب ...
who lost his son.
الذي فقد ابنه.
Drop the act!
إسقاط الفعل!
No matter what you say, it won't bring my son back.
بغض النظر عما تقوله ، لن يعيد ابني.
Answer me!
يجيبني!
Did he really deserve to die?
هل كان حقا يستحق الموت؟
You killed my son!
لقد قتلت ابني!
Let me go!
دعني اذهب!
Don't come into my room or touch my stuff without my permission. Understand?
لا تدخل غرفتي أو تلمس أشيائي بدون إذني.  تفهم؟
She gave it to me here,
أعطتني إياه هنا ،
and I put it in my bag.
ووضعته في حقيبتي.
Where the heck is it?
أين هو بحق الجحيم؟
YOUNGSAN SESAME OIL
زيت السمسم الشبابي
I'm feeling unwell. I need to get some rest.
أشعر بتوعك.  أنا بحاجة للحصول على قسط من الراحة.
YOUNGSAN TO SEOUL
من الشباب إلى سيول
Youngsan?
يونغسان؟
COLD MEDICINE
دواء بارد
ASSEMBLYMAN NAM JOONG-DO
نام جونج دو
Honey.
عسل.
I'm sorry. Did I startle you?
أنا آسف.  هل أذهلتك؟
Just leave it, honey. I'll clean it up.
فقط اتركه ، عزيزي.  سأقوم بتنظيفه.
-Just leave it. -It's okay.
-فقط دعها.  -حسنا.
Sorry, I'll make some again.
آسف ، سأقوم ببعضها مرة أخرى.
That's okay.
حسنا.
I'm going to head out.
انا ذاهب الى الخروج.
Right, Yoon-seo's class is visiting the National Assembly today.
حسنًا ، صف يون سيو يزور الجمعية الوطنية اليوم.
Right. That was today.
الصحيح.  كان ذلك اليوم.
Hold on.
يتمسك.
You're not running a fever.
أنت لا تصاب بالحمى.
You sounded sick yesterday, and you look really pale right now.
لقد بدوت مريضًا أمس وتبدو شاحبًا حقًا الآن.
No, I'm okay.
لا انا بخير.
Don't just say that. Go see a doctor later.
لا تقل ذلك فقط.  اذهب لرؤية الطبيب في وقت لاحق.
Okay.
تمام.
All right. See you later.
حسنا.  أراك لاحقًا.
SEUNG-HEE: COME TO THIS ADDRESS AT 7 P.M.
SEUNG-HEE: تعال إلى هذا العنوان الساعة 7 مساءً
Come in.
ادخل.
For breakfast and lunch…
للفطور والغداء ...
Right.
الصحيح.
I thought you forgot these.
اعتقدت أنك نسيت هذه.
Did you bring these from my studio?
هل أحضرت هذه من الاستوديو الخاص بي؟
Sorry?
آسف؟
Yes.
نعم.
I stopped by last night to look for my lip balm.
توقفت الليلة الماضية للبحث عن مرطب شفتي.
-Lip balm? -Yes, my lip balm.
-مرهم الشفة؟  - نعم ، مرطب شفتي.
I saw the passcode when you were opening the--
رأيت رمز المرور عندما كنت تفتح--
What did I tell you?
ماذا أخبرتك؟
I told you not to go into my space without my permission, didn't I?
قلت لك لا تذهب إلى الفضاء الخاص بي دون إذني ، أليس كذلك؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I'm just a kid you know. I shouldn't have gone into your space.
أنا مجرد طفل كما تعلم.  لا يجب أن أذهب إلى مساحتك.
But I only did so
لكنني فعلت ذلك فقط
because you didn't keep your promise about finding my lip balm.
لأنك لم تف بوعدك بإيجاد مرطب شفتي.
Aren't you taking these?
ألا تأخذ هذه؟
Should I put them back?
هل يجب علي إعادتهم؟
Or should I throw them away?
أم يجب أن أرميهم بعيدًا؟
There's a statue too.
يوجد تمثال أيضًا.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
It's huge.
انه ضخم.
Hello,
مرحبًا،
I'm Assemblyman Nam Joong-do of Sinyang.
أنا عضو الجمعية نام جونغ دو من Sinyang.
-You're awesome! -You're so handsome!
-انت رائع!  -انت وسيم جدا!
-You're so amazing! -It's nice to meet you!
-انت فعلا مدهش!  -من اللطيف مقابلتك!
How do you like being here?
كيف تحب التواجد هنا؟
-We love it! -It's so nice!
-نحن نحبها!  -انه جميل جدا!
-You're so cool! -You're amazing.
-أنت رائع جدا!  -أنت مذهل.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Hye-joo told you to bring this to me? Why isn't she using it at home?
أخبرتك هي-جو أن تحضر هذا لي؟  لماذا لا تستخدمها في المنزل؟
I'm not sure.
لست واثق.
All right.
حسنا.
It's all done.
انها فعلت كل.
Have some kalguksu as well next time, okay?
هل لديك بعض من kalguksu في المرة القادمة ، حسنًا؟
Thank you. Goodbye.
شكرًا لك.  مع السلامة.
Bye.
الوداع.
Pay up.
دفع ما يصل.
You need to pay for that.
عليك أن تدفع ثمن ذلك.
Ms. Hyeon, she didn't pay.
السيدة هيون ، لم تدفع.
Hey, why are you leaving without--
مرحبًا ، لماذا تغادر بدون--
Come back for some kalguksu, okay? Be careful not to spill that.
تعال لبعض kalguksu ، حسنا؟  احرص على عدم سكب ذلك.
-But-- -Go on.
-ولكن- -اذهب.
FREE FOOD FOR CHILDREN, TEENAGERS, AND PREGNANT WOMEN
طعام مجاني للأطفال والمراهقين والنساء الحوامل
Have you had lunch?
هل تناولت الغداء؟
Hello, it's nice to meet you.
أهلا من اللطيف مقابلتك.
It's nice to meet you.
من اللطيف مقابلتك.
Gosh.
يا الهي.
-This is so cool. -Nice to meet you.
-هذا رائع جدا.  -سعيد بلقائك.
-Your dad is so amazing. -I'm going to frame this.
-أبيك رائع جدا.  - سأقوم بتأطير هذا.
See you at home.
أراك في المنزل.
So you're Da-som.
إذن أنت دا سوم.
Hi.
أهلاً.
-Hello. -It's nice to meet you.
-مرحبًا.  -من اللطيف مقابلتك.
By the way, is this really your personal number?
بالمناسبة ، هل هذا حقًا رقمك الشخصي؟
Yes. Call that number, and I'll pick up.
نعم.  اتصل بهذا الرقم ، وسوف أستجيب.
No way.
مستحيل.
Do you give dating advice?
هل تقدم نصائح للمواعدة؟
I'm sorry, but I only do that on the weekends.
أنا آسف ، لكني أفعل ذلك فقط في عطلة نهاية الأسبوع.
Did you not have breakfast?
ألم تتناول الفطور؟
Then you get an extra.
ثم تحصل على مبلغ إضافي.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
You didn't know how things work here,
لم تكن تعرف كيف تعمل الأشياء هنا ،
so I don't blame you,
لذلك أنا لا ألومك
but it still bothers me
لكنه لا يزال يزعجني
that I couldn't explain it properly.
لم أستطع شرحه بشكل صحيح.
Lots of kids are coming by today.
سيأتي الكثير من الأطفال اليوم.
-Really? -Yes.
-هل حقا؟  -نعم.
I still wish more kids would stop by.
ما زلت أتمنى أن يتوقف المزيد من الأطفال.
Didn't you say Yoon-seo's grandmother gave you dumplings for free?
ألم تقل أن جدة يون سيو أعطتك الزلابية مجانًا؟
Yes.
نعم.
Whenever my mom was working late,
كلما كانت أمي تعمل لوقت متأخر ،
I'd come here by myself and ask for some dumplings.
أتيت إلى هنا بمفردي وأطلب بعض الزلابية.
And when my mom would hurry over to apologize and try to pay,
وعندما تسرع أمي للاعتذار وتحاول الدفع ،
she wouldn't take the money and she'd say children had to eat well.
لن تأخذ المال وتقول إن الأطفال يجب أن يأكلوا جيدًا.
And she would say that's what neighbors are for.
وكانت تقول أن هذا ما يريده الجيران.
When I came back to this neighborhood
عندما عدت إلى هذا الحي
and didn't know how to make ends meet,
ولم يكن يعرف كيف يكسبون قوت يومهم ،
she gave me a job here.
أعطتني وظيفة هنا.
I was truly grateful.
كنت حقا ممتنا.
Had she been around a bit longer,
لو كانت في الجوار لفترة أطول قليلاً ،
she would have seen her son become an assemblyman.
كانت سترى ابنها يصبح عضو مجلس.
Come to think of it,
تعال نفكر بها،
Assemblyman Nam must take after his mother.
عضو الجمعية نام يجب أن يأخذ بعد والدته.
Yeo-jin, can I take a couple bottles of that oil home?
يو جين ، هل يمكنني أخذ بضع زجاجات من هذا الزيت للمنزل؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
OPTIMIZATION OF SEX CRIME VICTIM SUPPORT
تحسين دعم ضحايا الجرائم الجنسية
PENALTY AND VICTIM SUPPORT FOR DIGITAL SEX CRIME
دعم العقوبة والضحايا في الجرائم الجنسية الرقمية
Sir,
سيد،
I'm sure you know, as a member of the Legislation and Judiciary Committee,
أنا متأكد من أنك تعلم ، بصفتك عضوًا في لجنة التشريع والقضاء ،
but there hasn't been a single proposed amendment regarding sex crimes
لكن لم يكن هناك تعديل مقترح واحد بخصوص جرائم الجنس
that passed the committee's review to be referred to the plenary session
التي اجتازت مراجعة اللجنة لإحالتها إلى الجلسة العامة
this year.
هذا العام.
With dozens of bills proposed every day in the National Assembly,
مع عشرات مشاريع القوانين المقترحة كل يوم في مجلس الأمة ،
it makes sense that not every one of them is discussed in depth.
من المنطقي عدم مناقشة كل واحد منهم بعمق.
My term will be over in a few months.
ستنتهي ولايتي في غضون بضعة أشهر.
All bills that fail to be passed by then
جميع الفواتير التي لا يتم تمريرها في ذلك الوقت
will automatically be disposed of.
سيتم التخلص منها تلقائيًا.
Right.
الصحيح.
If I'm being completely honest,
إذا كنت صادقًا تمامًا ،
unless a major case of sex crime occurs
ما لم تحدث قضية كبيرة من الجرائم الجنسية
that brings about
الذي يجلب
a great public uproar,
ضجة عامة كبيرة ،
it won't be easy to push ahead with a bill
لن يكون من السهل المضي قدمًا في فاتورة
in merely six months.
في ستة أشهر فقط.
I agree with her.
أتفق معها.
During Ji Seung-kyu's case,
خلال قضية Ji Seung-kyu ،
the public demanded severe punishment for sex offenders…
طالب الجمهور بعقوبة شديدة لمرتكبي الجرائم الجنسية ...
But it didn't last long.
لكنها لم تدم طويلا.
We live in Dynamic Korea where we have a new headline every day.
نحن نعيش في كوريا الديناميكية حيث لدينا عنوان جديد كل يوم.
Sir, it's time for you to visit the district office.
سيدي ، حان الوقت لكي تزور مكتب المنطقة.
Okay.
تمام.
Why are you still here?
لماذا لا تزال هنا؟
I haven't paid.
لم ادفع.
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
No, I want to pay.
لا ، أريد أن أدفع.
We don't charge pregnant women either.
نحن لا نفرض رسومًا على النساء الحوامل أيضًا.
You didn't read it thoroughly, did you?
أنت لم تقرأه جيدًا ، أليس كذلك؟
FREE FOOD FOR CHILDREN, TEENAGERS, AND PREGNANT WOMEN
طعام مجاني للأطفال والمراهقين والنساء الحوامل
Did you think I didn't charge you last time
هل تعتقد أنني لم أحاسبك آخر مرة
because you were pregnant with Ji-hoon's child?
لأنك كنت حاملاً بطفل جي-هون؟
Although that's also true.
على الرغم من أن هذا صحيح أيضًا.
Either way,
اما الطريقة،
I'm glad you can eat our dumplings despite your morning sickness.
أنا سعيد لأنك تستطيع أن تأكل الزلابية على الرغم من غثيان الصباح.
Come by whenever you want.
تعال متى شئت.
Okay.
تمام.
YEO-JIN
YEO-JIN
-Hey, Yeo-jin. -Hey, Hye-joo. It's me.
مرحبًا ، يو جين.  - هاي جو.  هذا أنا.
I received the oil.
لقد استلمت الزيت.
Are you sure you want me to use it here?
هل أنت متأكد أنك تريدني أن أستخدمه هنا؟
Why aren't you using it at home?
لماذا لا تستخدمه في المنزل؟
I mean, you can give some to Yeong-seon.
أعني ، يمكنك إعطاء البعض ليونغ سون.
-I already did. -Oh, my goodness.
-لقد فعلتها.  -يا إلهي.
-…hit a motorcycle by the Cheongdam Bridge -Goodness.
- ... اصطدم بدراجة نارية بجسر تشيونجدام - طيب.
-around 1 a.m. -What is it?
-حوالي 1 صباحا -ما هو؟
-and drove away. -My gosh.
وابتعدوا.  -يا إلهي.
Do you know Ko Ji-seop from the Daehan Party?
هل تعرف كو جي سيوب من حزب دايهان؟
Anyway, his wife drove off
على أي حال ، انطلقت زوجته بالسيارة
after running a man over and killing him.
بعد أن دهس رجلاً وقتله.
Oh, my.
أوه يا.
-They can't reach him right now. -The police
-لا يمكنهم الوصول إليه الآن.  -الشرطة
analyzed the CCTV footage…
حللوا لقطات كاميرات المراقبة ...
Of course I feel bad about the victim,
بالطبع أشعر بالسوء تجاه الضحية ،
but I'm worried about her husband. He's a politician.
لكني قلقة على زوجها.  إنه سياسي.
Ms. Woo, please give us a comment on the current situation.
السيدة وو ، من فضلك أعطنا تعليقًا على الوضع الحالي.
-Yes? -Your car is waiting out front, sir.
-نعم؟  سيارتك تنتظر بالخارج يا سيدي.
Okay, thank you.
حسنا شكرا لك.
See you later.
أراك لاحقًا.
The wife of Assemblyman Ko Ji-seop of the Daehan Party
زوجة عضو الجمعية كو جي سيوب من حزب دايهان
hit a delivery bike with her foreign car, killing the rider.
صدمت دراجة توصيل بسيارتها الأجنبية ، مما أسفر عن مقتل الفارس.
The accident occurred on the Cheongdam Bridge
وقع الحادث على جسر تشيونجدام
at 1 a.m. three days ago and is causing an uproar.
الساعة 1 صباحًا قبل ثلاثة أيام وتسبب ضجة.
-See you tomorrow. -The police analyzed the CCTV footage
-أراك غدا.  - قامت الشرطة بتحليل لقطات كاميرات المراقبة
-and has arrested Ko's wife. -Goodbye.
- واعتقلت زوجة كو.  -مع السلامة.
Do you really think Assemblyman Ko didn't know?
هل تعتقد حقًا أن عضو الجمعية كو لم يكن يعرف؟
I'm not sure.
لست واثق.
They really need to keep their family in line.
إنهم يحتاجون حقًا للحفاظ على عائلاتهم في الطابور.
Their careers could end from one mistake by their family.
يمكن أن تنتهي حياتهم المهنية من خطأ واحد من قبل أسرهم.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
-Hello.
-مرحبًا.  -مرحبًا.
ASSEMBLYMAN KO JI-SEOP
ASSEMBLYMAN KO JI-SEOP
Poor Assemblyman Ko.
كو.
Assemblyman Nam is lucky to have Ms. Kim as his wife.
عضو الجمعية نام محظوظ لأن السيدة كيم كانت زوجته.
She may not help at all, but she doesn't cause any trouble either.
قد لا تساعد على الإطلاق ، لكنها لا تسبب أي مشكلة أيضًا.
But when a quiet person causes a problem, it tends to be a huge one.
ولكن عندما يتسبب شخص هادئ في مشكلة ، فإنها تميل إلى أن تكون مشكلة ضخمة.
Come on.
تعال.
Be careful what you say.
كن حذرا ما تقوله.
Still, she's not the type
ومع ذلك ، فهي ليست من النوع
who'd cause trouble.
الذي قد يسبب المتاعب.
Right, Mr. Jang?
صحيح يا سيد جانغ؟
Yes, let's hope so.
نعم ، دعونا نأمل ذلك.
WOO JIN-SEOK PRESSURES KO JI-SEOP TO STEP DOWN
يضغط WOO JIN-SEOK على KO JI-SEOP للتراجع
SERIES OF CONTROVERSIES IN THE DAEHAN PARTY
سلسلة الخلافات في حزب ظهران
INCOMING CALL
مكالمة واردة
Why aren't you picking up?
لماذا لا تلتقط؟
Hey, Seung-hee.
مرحبًا سيونغ هي.
You weren't picking up.
لم تكن تلتقط.
It stopped ringing just as I was picking up.
توقف عن الرنين عندما كنت أتحمل.
-But Seung-hee-- -You're coming to Youngsan later, right?
- لكن سونغ هي - أنت قادم إلى يونغسان لاحقًا ، أليس كذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
Okay.
تمام.
You didn't reply to my texts,
لم ترد على نصوصي ،
so I thought you weren't coming.
لذلك اعتقدت أنك لن تأتي.
So I thought,
لذلك اعتقدت ،
"Did she run away again?"
"هل هربت مرة أخرى؟"
"She's making things more interesting."
"إنها تجعل الأشياء أكثر إثارة للاهتمام."
No, I'm coming to Youngsan.
لا ، أنا قادم إلى يونغسان.
I'll be there.
سأكون هناك.
All right. See you later.
حسنا.  أراك لاحقًا.
See that greenhouse over there?
ترى تلك الدفيئة هناك؟
-You'd be buying that much. -But we don't even know
-أنت تشتري هذا القدر.  -لكننا لا نعرف حتى
if the road will be built there.
إذا كان الطريق سيبنى هناك.
Goodness, ma'am.
الخير يا سيدتي.
The price has already doubled since last month.
تضاعف السعر بالفعل منذ الشهر الماضي.
It'll skyrocket if a road really gets built.
سوف يرتفع بشكل صاروخي إذا تم بناء طريق حقًا.
You were taking so long that I thought you left.
لقد كنت تستغرق وقتًا طويلاً حتى ظننت أنك غادرت.
Were you talking to your husband again?
هل كنت تتحدثين مع زوجك مرة أخرى؟
No.
لا.
Gosh, she must be very happily married.
يا إلهي ، يجب أن تكون متزوجة بسعادة كبيرة.
Who cares?
من يهتم؟
She's so happy with her husband that she neglects her old mother.
إنها سعيدة جدًا بزوجها لدرجة أنها تتجاهل والدتها العجوز.
-Mom. -Hey, I don't need you either.
-أم.  -مرحبًا ، أنا لست بحاجة إليك أيضًا.
I'm going to meet my friends.
سألتقي بأصدقائي.
So go to your husband.
لذا اذهبي إلى زوجك.
Mr. Park, let's go.
السيد بارك ، دعنا نذهب.
-See you tomorrow. -Bye.
-أراك غدا.  -الوداع.
SONMAT NOODLES
سونمات نودلز
Hello, sir.
أهلاً سيدي.
-Hello.
-مرحبًا.  -مرحبًا.
-I'm rooting for you. -I appreciate it.
- أنا أتجذر من أجلك.  -أنا أقدر ذلك.
-You can do it. -Thank you.
-يمكنك أن تفعل ذلك.  -شكرًا لك.
THE COMPETENT ASSEMBLYMAN! WE BELIEVE IN YOU, NAM JOONG-DO
عضو الجمعية المختصة!  نحن نؤمن بك ، نام جونج دو
Ma'am.
أملك
Goodness, Assemblyman Nam.
الخير ، عضو الجمعية نام.
-Ma'am, what are you doing here? -What the…
-أمى ، ماذا تفعلين هنا؟  -ماذا…
-Well… -Assemblyman Nam.
-حسنا ... -عضو الجمعية نام.
Goodness.
صلاح.
Ma'am, you're cleaning out here again?
سيدتي ، أنت تنظفين هنا مرة أخرى؟
You should just come inside and have some tea.
يجب عليك فقط الدخول وشرب بعض الشاي.
I'm forever grateful to you,
أنا ممتن لك إلى الأبد ،
so I wanted to give you something,
لذلك أردت أن أعطيك شيئًا ،
but they told me you couldn't accept any gifts.
لكنهم قالوا لي إنك لا تستطيع قبول أي هدايا.
There's nothing else I could do for you.
لا يوجد شيء آخر يمكنني القيام به من أجلك.
It's no big deal, so don't worry about me.
إنها ليست مشكلة كبيرة ، لذلك لا تقلق علي.
Sir.
سيد.
Oh, no.
أوه لا.
That's a dirty rag.
هذه قطعة قماش قذرة.
Goodness. Sir.
صلاح.  سيد.
Thanks to you,
شكرا لك،
that bastard got what he deserved.
حصل ذلك اللقيط على ما يستحقه.
And now,
و الأن،
I'm finally at peace.
أنا أخيرًا في سلام.
I'll repay your kindness at all costs.
سأدفع لطفك بأي ثمن.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Thank you so much.
شكرا جزيلا لك.
Get home safely.
الحصول على المنزل بأمان.
Goodbye, ma'am.
وداعا سيدتي.
She doesn't know yet.
هي لا تعرف بعد.
That bastard uploaded the video
هذا اللقيط حمل الفيديو
right before he jumped.
قبل أن يقفز مباشرة.
When the arrest warrant was applied for,
عندما تم تقديم طلب الاعتقال ،
he had only threatened to leak it.
لقد هدد فقط بتسريبه.
Then the case was closed following his death.
ثم أغلقت القضية بعد وفاته.
So no one knew about the leak until later on.
لذلك لم يعرف أحد بشأن التسريب حتى وقت لاحق.
Has it spread widely?
هل انتشرت على نطاق واسع؟
The police are still hunting down whoever redistributes it.
لا تزال الشرطة تطارد كل من يعيد توزيعها.
The specialist you personally hired
الأخصائي الذي وظفته شخصيًا
is working to remove all the videos.
تعمل على إزالة جميع الفيديوهات.
But it's not easy to get rid of all of them in such a short time.
لكن ليس من السهل التخلص منها جميعًا في مثل هذا الوقت القصير.
It's a relief that the case isn't in the spotlight anymore.
من المريح أن القضية لم تعد في دائرة الضوء بعد الآن.
She's so elated that he got what he deserved.
إنها مبتهجة للغاية لدرجة أنه حصل على ما يستحقه.
If she hears about the video on the news…
إذا سمعت عن الفيديو في الأخبار ...
She'll be utterly shocked.
سوف تصاب بصدمة شديدة.
For her sake, there shouldn't be any follow-up articles
من أجلها ، لا ينبغي أن يكون هناك أي مقالات متابعة
that draw attention to this case again.
التي تلفت الانتباه إلى هذه الحالة مرة أخرى.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
We can't have that happen.
لا يمكننا أن يحدث ذلك.
1 JEONGMIMUL-RO 2-GIL, YOUNGSAN-SI
1 JEONGMIMUL-RO 2-GIL ، YOUNGSAN-SI
YOUNGSAN
يونغسان
We have a total of 370 members as of today.
لدينا ما مجموعه 370 عضوا حتى اليوم.
That's a ten-percent increase in new members compared to last month.
هذه زيادة بنسبة 10 بالمائة في الأعضاء الجدد مقارنة بالشهر الماضي.
And it's on a steady rise.
وهي في ارتفاع مستمر.
We have a more luxurious interior and better equipment
لدينا تصميم داخلي أكثر فخامة ومعدات أفضل
compared to our competitors.
مقارنة بمنافسينا.
That's believed to be the main factor that attracts customers.
يُعتقد أن هذا هو العامل الرئيسي الذي يجذب العملاء.
Good work.
عمل جيد.
Please make sure our customers can exercise
يرجى التأكد من أن عملائنا يمكنهم ممارسة الرياضة
in a pleasant environment at all times.
في بيئة ممتعة في جميع الأوقات.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Hey, Seung-hee. It's me.
مرحبًا سيونغ هي.  هذا أنا.
Since your mother is meeting her friends this evening,
بما أن والدتك ستلتقي بأصدقائها هذا المساء ،
how about you and I go out for dinner?
ماذا عنك وأنا نخرج لتناول العشاء؟
I see. You already have plans?
أرى.  لديك بالفعل خطط؟
With a friend?
مع صديق؟
Okay.
تمام.
Have fun.
استمتع.
I'll see you at home.
سأراك في المنزل.
Okay. Bye.
تمام.  الوداع.
A friend?
صديق؟
Welcome to Youngsan, a city full of love and happiness.
مرحبًا بكم في يونغسان ، المدينة المليئة بالحب والسعادة.
YOUNGSAN CHILDREN'S HOME
منزل الأطفال الصغار
Seung-ho.
سيونغ هو
I asked you last time not to show up like this.
طلبت منك في المرة الأخيرة ألا تظهر هكذا.
Do you not like me?
هل لا تحبني؟
Why not?
لما لا؟
Seung-ho, you see…
سيونغ هو ، كما ترى ...
I've never thought of you to be more than Seung-hee's brother.
لم أفكر أبدًا في أنك أكثر من شقيق سونغ هي.
So I'm asking you. Please.
لذلك أنا أسألك.  رجاء.
Don't come here again.
لا تأتي إلى هنا مرة أخرى.
Bye.
الوداع.
Kim Jae-eun.
كيم جاي يون.
Seung-ho, please let go of me.
سيونغ هو ، من فضلك اتركني.
Okay?
تمام؟
ON DUTY FOR YOUR SAFETY AND HAPPINESS YOUNGSAN POLICE STATION
واجب من أجل سلامتك وسعادتك في مركز شرطة يونغ سان
Hey, kid.
يا طفل.
Is something wrong? Do you need help?
هل هناك خطأ؟  هل تحتاج مساعدة؟
Hey, is that blood on your clothes?
مهلا ، هل هذا الدم على ملابسك؟
Hey!
يا!
I'd like an apology.
أود الاعتذار.
And please stay away from me.
ورجاء ابتعد عني.
Pardon?
عفو؟
Boys can be like that
يمكن للأولاد أن يكونوا هكذا
when they like someone.
عندما يحبون شخصًا ما.
And I'll be blunt.
وسأكون صريحا.
Nothing really happened.
لم يحدث شيء حقًا.
You just scraped your palms and knees.
لقد كشطت راحتي يديك وركبتيك.
That's…
هذا ...
That's because I ran away.
هذا لأنني هربت.
If I hadn't, I would have…
لو لم أفعل ، لكنت ...
Here.
هنا.
Take this, okay?
خذ هذا ، حسنا؟
I understand that you're hurt and upset right now,
أتفهم أنك مجروح ومستاء الآن ،
But can you just pretend that you briefly went out
لكن هل يمكنك فقط التظاهر بأنك خرجت لفترة وجيزة
with a law student from Seoul National University?
مع طالب قانون من جامعة سيول الوطنية؟
Let me go.
دعني اذهب.
I'll…
مريض…
I'll get you a scholarship to Gyeongji University.
سأحضر لك منحة دراسية إلى جامعة Gyeongji.
My husband's aunt is the chairwoman there.
عمة زوجي هي الرئيسة هناك.
How will you pay your tuition
كيف ستدفع الرسوم الدراسية الخاصة بك
when you don't have parents?
عندما لا يكون لديك والدين؟
I'll make sure you get that scholarship.
سوف أتأكد من حصولك على تلك المنحة.
So let's not make a big deal out of nothing, okay?
لذلك دعونا لا نجعل صفقة كبيرة من لا شيء ، حسنًا؟
I'll…
مريض…
take the scholarship then.
خذ المنحة الدراسية بعد ذلك.
Okay.
تمام.
I'll make sure you get it.
سوف أتأكد من حصولك عليه.
The scholarship.
المنح الدراسية.
Kim Jae-eun.
كيم جاي يون.
Don't be mistaken.
لا تكن مخطئا.
It's not like I actually liked you.
ليس الأمر كما لو كنت معجبًا بك بالفعل.
If you needed money, you should have just said so.
إذا كنت بحاجة إلى المال ، كان يجب أن تقول ذلك للتو.
You pathetic orphan.
أنت يتيم مثير للشفقة.
JIN SEUNG-HO OF YOUNGSAN HIGH SCHOOL ACCEPTED TO SNU SCHOOL OF LAW
تم قبول JIN SEUNG-HO من YOUNGSAN HIGH SCHOOL في SNU SCHOOL OF LAW
But can you just pretend that you briefly went out
لكن هل يمكنك فقط التظاهر بأنك خرجت لفترة وجيزة
with a law student from Seoul National University?
مع طالب قانون من جامعة سيول الوطنية؟
Jin Seung-ho.
جين سيونغ هو.
Twenty years ago,
قبل عشرين عاما ،
the day my life was
اليوم الذي كانت فيه حياتي
turned upside down for the very first time…
انقلب رأسًا على عقب للمرة الأولى ...
You killed him.
قتلته.
You murderer.
أنت قاتل.
My Seung-ho…
سيونغ هو ...
My poor baby…
طفلي المسكين…
My goodness, Seung-ho…
يا إلهي ، سيونغ هو ...
JIN SEUNG-HO OF YOUNGSAN HIGH SCHOOL ACCEPTED TO SNU SCHOOL OF LAW
تم قبول JIN SEUNG-HO من YOUNGSAN HIGH SCHOOL في SNU SCHOOL OF LAW
YOUNGSAN TO GANGNAM
YOUNGSAN إلى GANGNAM
The only thing I could do…
الشيء الوحيد الذي يمكنني فعله ...
was to run away.
كان على الهروب.
KO JI-SEOP'S WIFE CAUSES BIGGEST CRISIS OF HIS CAREER
تسبب زوجة KO JI-SEOP أكبر أزمة في حياته المهنية
I never thought I would come back.
لم اعتقد ابدا انني سأعود.
ILHWADANG
إيلوادانغ
There she is.
ها هي ذا.
Honey.
عسل.
You made it.
لقد فعلتها.
TROLLEY
عربة
This is between us. My husband--
هذا بيننا.  زوجي--
Your husband is an assemblyman, no less, and the elections are coming up.
زوجك عضو مجلس لا أقل والانتخابات مقبلة.
Should I put up banners and hand out fliers about what you did?
هل يجب أن أضع لافتات وأوزع منشورات حول ما فعلته؟
My wife will not have any influence over my political activities.
لن يكون لزوجتي أي تأثير على أنشطتي السياسية.
I know it's too late, but I have to do something.
أعلم أن الوقت قد فات ، لكن علي أن أفعل شيئًا.
Let's do one thing at a time, shall we?
لنفعل شيئًا واحدًا في كل مرة ، أليس كذلك؟
Why did she have to get involved?
لماذا كان عليها أن تتدخل؟
You. Can you take responsibility?
أنت.  هل يمكنك تحمل المسؤولية؟
You're one to talk.
أنت واحد للتحدث.
Why do you want to know?
لماذا تريد أن تعرف؟
Is there something you find suspicious?
هل هناك شيء تجده مريبًا؟
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim
ترجمة الترجمة: سو جي كيم